Comment in the chat if you can hear me.
Yeah. Yeah. I, I can hear you.
Oh, awesome dude. Awesome. Welcome.
Uh, I think this is the first time you've jumped on a live,
Uh, yeah. I've got a little
bit of free time here right now,
and I saw the notification come in that slack,
so just, uh, thought I'd hop on.
But yeah, I'm, I'm new to your program.
I love it, man. Welcome, welcome. Stoked to have you here.
Um, uh, what is it that you do, man, in terms
of, um, creative?
Are you, are you a creative or are
you a business owner or both?
Uh, I am a business owner learning
to be a creative.
Ooh. So love that.
Yeah. Um, now my, uh, my wife, her family
and I, we own, uh, five Korean restaurants in San Francisco.
Um, we have a soju cocktail bar.
That's the one I'm mainly, uh, involved in.
And, uh, about a year back, uh, unexpectedly, we had
to relocate, uh, our soju bar to another part of town,
more residential.
And, uh, very, very shortly we realized we had to get, uh,
really good at, uh, having a presence online.
Mm-Hmm. Um, and we had, uh, hired a third party company
to do a lot of our social media and editing
and content creating and all that, all that jazz.
Um, they, uh, it was a father and a son.
The son decided to go his own direction.
And, um, so they're, they're not really doing it anymore.
But, uh, I just, I gotta take on,
I gotta take on that task now.
So I, um, you know, all the, how should I say,
part of this, my reasoning for joining your course also is,
uh, while we were closed, uh, I've really started
to dive into the whole Amazon FBA
and just releasing products and how to get, uh, the content
and how to get the graphics and everything for,
uh, product launches.
Mm-Hmm. Um, we, we have, you know, we can, so we can source
a lot of items for the food and beverage, uh, industry,
but there are others that, uh, we can, um,
we can source also.
So kind of trying to kill two birds with one stone here.
Yeah. Making some pretty cool graphics, pretty cool content
for the, uh, restaurant side of things.
But in addition to, once we decide to, uh,
do some product launches on, uh, Amazon, uh, this is,
you know, the, I, I hope I'm in the right
place. So, but yes.
Yeah. That's amazing, man.
Uh, it sounds like you, you have a lot,
you have a lot going on.
Um, so running five different restaurants.
My wife is Korean, so like,
I don't know if you have any Korean, like influences.
Oh, wow. But,
but I'd love to eat at one of your restaurants one
day. Yeah.
Oh, man. Well, first things first, their,
their food is amazing.
Um, and, uh, very hardworking people
and very, uh, uh, like to, uh, you know, community driven,
like to be around family
and friends, you know, when you eat and never eating alone.
Yeah. When you eat, always some soju when you're on the
table, you know? For
Sure. Um,
But, uh, but yeah, me personally, I'm, I'm a,
I'm half Caucasian, half Hispanic.
Mm-Hmm. Uh, I'm still new to the whole K-pop world and KDRs
and that whole deal.
I'm, I'm, I'm learning as I go,
but, um, yeah, I don't if, if you're ever in San Francisco
or wherever, wherever you're from, we actually have,
once a month we throw pretty big, uh,
k-pop parties at our restaurant.
Oh, fun. And those, those are, those,
those go kind of crazy.
That's awesome, man. Well, I, I'm in, I'm in SoCal,
so like, going up to ssf is, you know, it's a,
it's a an hour long plane ride, and Oh, me
and my family go up there every now and then.
But if we, if we ever end up going up there,
I'm gonna hit you up and we're gonna, we're gonna do some,
uh, do some eating and, and, and drinking,
but, um, but that's awesome, man.
It's, so, it just sounds, it sounds like
to me you have a lot of different businesses,
or you have your core businesses going on.
Um, you're looking for new opportunities, uh,
to get possibly into the e-comm space, if I'm not mistaken.
Correct. So right now, you're just kind
of like taking in a lot of new information,
maybe finding new ways to adapt, um,
and also execute on your own,
because you used to have people who were doing it for you,
it's no longer the, the case.
Um, so it, it sounds like you're like, okay, it's game time.
Like I, I need to, I need
to figure something out. Is that right? Yeah,
Yeah. A a absolutely.
I've, from what I've seen in regards
to just how we've had to put a little more energy
and focus on our, our social media online presence Mm-Hmm.
There is definitely a demand for this, uh, this skill
that the short form graphics editing, video editing content,
um, when, when we had our third party team working with us,
we, we were getting dms every day.
Oh, who's doing your social media?
Oh, who, who are you working with?
Can you, can you guys run our, our social media? Mm-Hmm.
So, I guess kind of from the high level down is,
is really a, a skill I need to learn, um, you know,
the Premier pro
and at least being able to capture something good,
or being able to build something with a, a graphic
that catches the eye, you know, in
less than three seconds type of deal.
And, um, once, once I'm pretty confident in that skill,
then I can, uh, kind of really identify where, where I want
to implement that skill, whether it's our own restaurants
or whether it's, um, you know, an Amazon or, or,
or something else yet, yet to be identified.
So, for sure, for sure. Yeah. That's where I'm at.
I love it. Well, I think you're,
you are in the right place for sure.
We have a ton of, we have a ton of creatives
and ton of entrepreneurs who are all either trying
to build businesses, trying to improve their skills, trying
to, um, you know, just level up.
And what it sounds like to me is, um, you know,
organic is, is is where your focus is at.
You're not, you're not running any
ads right now, is that right?
Uh, at the moment I'm not. Got it.
Uh, I, I do have a, a background in ads.
I'm, I, uh, come from an insurance based background.
I was running, uh, ads for an,
a national reseller of Medicare leads.
Um, I don't know, our ad spend was maybe
25, 3500 a day Mm-Hmm.
That I would manage. Um,
and that was all kind of like right before Covid.
Hmm. So, um, I, I do have a background in that,
but in regards to an actual ads for our restaurant
or ads for products, um, we don't,
we don't have any active ads at the moment.
Got it. Um, so
before I kind of like start maybe adding, adding steps
or value or strategy to, um, your business,
I just wanna get a little bit more clarity on it.
Um, okay. But, um, so are you focused
primarily on your, uh, promoting your restaurants?
'cause there's five, right? Are they all independent
of each other, or are they all related?
Yeah, they're all different styles of Korean cuisine.
They are each individual, uh, brands.
I see. So, Yeah.
One, uh, well, actually one brand has two locations.
Uh, uh, kind of a, um, like a Korean Chipotle, you know,
kind of build your bowl bebo Bebe Bowl style.
Okay. Nice. Uh, we have another one that is more
of like the spicy seafood Mm-Hmm.
Uh, brand that's called, uh, soul Soup Company,
sold like a Seoul, Korea.
Um, John Pong is the style of soup that that one is. Mm-Hmm.
So, uh, and then we have another one that's, uh, like a grab
and go, uh, chobo, the, like the little tofu skin pockets
with like, um, proteins on top.
And we have boba at that location.
Uh, and then, but the one where, where we need the, where,
how should I say, the one that, that give nets us,
the biggest return on the energy is the Soju cocktail bar.
That one's called the Corner Store with AK.
That's, that's really the one I have my most, most,
uh, my hands on.
Everything else is, is run from different family members.
I see. So the corner store is like your,
your most profitable one?
Uh, correct. We've, we've just got a bigger space.
We've got a full kitchen, we've got a full liquor license.
All the other ones are really more like fast
casual, grab and go items.
Mm-Hmm. Um, you know, maybe, you know, we'll get catering,
GrubHub, DoorDash, that type of deal.
But, um, yeah, we're the, in regards to
where our investment is most of our investment is,
and just the, the, the price per guest,
the price per ticket, um, you know, it would,
it would be the corner store.
Got it. Okay. So, okay.
I see your, I see your spot right now.
So what is, I'm just curious from the, um,
like what you guys offer.
Is it like, it's like a full event, it looks like a bar.
Are you, are you, are you in our Instagram?
I'm on your, I'm on your site right now. Um, is this it?
That, that's it. Awesome.
So this, that, that video was from one of, uh,
a private event that we booked.
Okay. That was, uh, there was like four guys that all kind
of came together and threw their birthday party sick.
Um, but if you go to the top right click on the Instagram,
um, shortcut Mm-Hmm.
This will probably give you a better idea of,
of what we got.
So, um, some of those flyers that's kind of just with me
and really one of our customers, he's,
he lives right across the street from us.
He seems to be pretty good at, at
that you can see some influencers
that we've done actually Yeah.
Hit that, uh, the glass
or the, even the girl, you can see what our, um,
previous media team did.
Got it. Yeah. This is, that's my brother-in-Law Ryan.
And there's our Somac one-on-one, one-on-one.
Yeah. These are sick. This is, there's a lot of music.
I'm gonna turn it off. This, this is a little loud,
but, um, yeah.
Yeah. That's pretty dope. I like that.
Um, yeah, these are, this is my next question was, um,
like, yeah, I was imagining things point of like, like reels
that are either informational, educational, you know,
show off the food, um, all of this,
The restaurant, All of this is really good.
Uh, so my question is, are you currently
managing the creative like, strategy for all of this?
Uh, well, here, I'll, um, I'll walk, I'll walk you
through the process.
So if you go to kind of scroll down
and I'll show you which one to pick.
So previously our, our third party company Mm-Hmm.
Um, was the one really doing the storyboarding
and the scheduling and when to put, uh, informational posts,
when to put like tips
or, you know, um, just the, the vi the vision
of, of the post.
Yeah. However, when his son decided to, to step away,
he we're, we're in the process of
building kind of like our own media arm.
Got it. So the father who doesn't really do the editing
or the, um, or the camera worker, anything like that, we,
uh, he's, hi, him and my wife
and I are kind of creating this new,
new company, I guess you call it.
Mm-Hmm. Uh, and we're ju we're build,
we're building it out on how to really propose it
to other restaurants
and other businesses that have already reached out to us.
So, but in, in reality, we've, we've got a lot of legwork
to, to go on that.
Yeah. I know somebody in our circle is gonna have to learn
how to do all this, basically what his son did.
Yeah. Um, and,
and either it being with our own content that we capture
with our own videos and, and cameras,
or if we build it out like a, like a graphic, um,
you know, yeah.
You can see like the short form stuff.
And then, uh,
there's one more I wanted to show you real quick.
Mm-Hmm. This is kind of where we really like picked it off.
Okay. Um, scroll down.
Uh, keep going, keep going. Okay. Well, whoa.
Pick, go up a little bit. Mm-Hmm.
Um, a little bit, little bit.
Click on, try that.
The one on the, see the one that says one soju party? Yeah.
Click on the, click on the
one on the right to the right of that.
Okay. It should be, it should be wide screen,
This guy. Okay.
Uh, yep. Here we go. And you can leave the volume on.
It's fun. Your neighbor.
Damn. It is wild, dude.
Good stuff. Huh? If I, yeah, if I, uh,
if I had known about this place
before kids, I'd be all upon it.
Yeah. So,
But I really like this.
Um, it has a very k-pop vibe, you know, very, very fun.
Um, Mm-Hmm. Inviting experience.
It's like, you get, you see what it's all about, you know?
Um, so I, I mean,
I think this media team did a pretty good job, um,
at least conveying what it is that you guys have to offer.
And, um, Mm-Hmm mm-Hmm.
I think keeping the culture tight around it.
Um, but yeah, I think the biggest thing right now is,
you know, you're, you need, you need a full-time video guy,
um, shooting content
E Exactly. Well,
there, there's kind of two layers to that.
So the idea is we wanna be able to offer kind of this
higher end, like, cinematic product
or service to one.
We would use it for our restaurants and our brands,
but also to be able to offer it to other, uh, you know,
we have, uh, some hotels that have reached out to us.
We've had some wineries reach out to us.
We've had, um, even like alcohol brands. Yeah.
Uh, like a, a, uh, a whiskey brand, a vodka brand.
Um, so part of the offering that again, would have,
I'm, I'm getting caught up on the skill to be able
to, to sell this.
Yeah. But, um, part of the offering would be, you know,
this kind of experiential, high quality, uh,
high production Yeah.
Uh, service to offer.
But then also another kind of like, level below
that would be, um, more like product
or informational content or, or a short form content Yeah.
To, to highlight the actual like, you know, um, the product.
Like let's say a a a 18 year whiskey
or, um, you know, high-end vodka or Yeah.
Uh, um, you, you know, event, event space at a
banquet room at a hotel.
Right. So kind of like two layers of what we would
offer Yeah.
Uh, to, to prospecting clients.
I love it. So this is right up my alley.
'cause like, I got my experience,
or like I've, I've productized video as a service Mm-Hmm.
Uh, and I've been doing it for like five
years, but, um, nice.
But yeah, so the way I see it as a business opportunity is,
um, is like, yeah.
The, I would say restaurants specifically,
or like events are definitely underutilized as like,
you know, there's, there's a lot of space here
to develop a service around Mm-Hmm.
Organic promo content that, you know, basically
what your previous team was doing.
Um, you know, this is a good like,
retainer model business too.
Um, and Okay.
And that you can basically, so like, um, I, I used
to have employees, uh, they started their own, uh,
their own type of business similar
to this, where they go Mm-Hmm.
To restaurants, and then they will film, you know,
a a month's worth of content and then they'll edit it,
and then they'll post it, uh,
for different food companies, restaurants and such.
And, you know, they'll make them very social friendly.
Um Mm-Hmm. And it's two guys right now, I think they have,
like, you know, they have, I don't, I don't know
how many brands they, or companies they have,
but if you were
to do something like this within the local area,
like you would basically just need to find videographers
and editors who either are a contract
or you wanted to bring them on full-time,
and then they would manage the, the execution process of it.
Mm-Hmm. And then you could manage like the, the
communication between the restaurants and stuff.
'cause that's more of like the high level type of,
you would do the sales and you would do the organization
and the operation side.
Mm-Hmm. But you would, you would have your own production
creative team to do the execution, the planning,
storyboarding, um, and then, and then, yeah.
Essentially I would break it into different packages
and tiers that whatever the, um, you know, depending on the,
the business and their size, it's like, okay, if you want us
to post seven times a week, right.
Like, at the most, I think at the highest level,
you could post three times a day
every single day for a month.
Right. Which would be nine times 30, which is like 90,
90 pieces of content, which is a lot.
Right, right, right. You know, um,
and then you would be like, okay,
we're somewhere in the middle, and then where's like a
starting, it's like, okay, well, we can post three times a
week for you and for this much this price.
Um, Mm-Hmm. So that's kind of, is that, is that something
that is aligned Yes. Kind of with what you're looking
To do? Yeah, definitely.
That's definitely what we're, what we're in the process
of building out my, um, is my, my wife myself,
and, um, the father of the third party guy's name is Jay.
Cool. Um, yeah.
We're, we're absolutely, we, we have a, well, couple things.
One, and,
and part part of this, uh, birthing
of this new media company is just, uh, you know, how,
how are we really kind of structuring our own expenses Hmm.
In regards to if it's a, you know, if it's a 10 99 person,
if it's AW two person
or, uh, you know, even how do we price this out without,
you know, one, you know, in the beginning, I get it,
we're probably gonna leave some money on the table in the
beginning, but we don't really wanna stay in that position.
Mm-Hmm. Uh, you know, where, where, when it comes
to the packages that are offering, um, you know, just how,
you know, he, he told us like the initial price was
like five grand a month.
Mm-Hmm. What? That they were charging when we onboard,
when they onboarded us Yep.
Initially. But now, um,
there's a lot more that we're gonna be doing.
There's a lot more we can help, especially, you know,
when we're, we haven't run ads at all,
but we will,
when we bring on clients under this media company, um,
you know, web development, you know, all kinds
of crazy stuff, but, awesome.
So I guess, I guess if I could,
I don't know if there's anyone else on the call here if I
don't wanna take up too much of the time, but, uh, yeah.
Um, so I guess, so here, here's some of the things
that we're kind of already trying
to just put on the timeline on what to address.
Mm-Hmm. So there are a couple of, well, mainly the people
that wanna work with us have,
including Jay himself, how we even met Jay.
They were all our regulars.
They're all our customers at the restaurant.
Awesome. So They
Know it, they, they live and breathe it.
They know, they understand it really well.
Yeah, exactly.
And, um, like even on our Instagram, we have a couple flyers
for some of the K-pop nights and stuff like that.
That was, uh, yeah, that was another one of our customers.
His name's, uh, Lex.
Um, you know, they, they put all that stuff together.
So from just like trying to figure these struc this,
this business structure out with Jay,
he said his son would spend about an hour
and a half of edit time for each, like seven
to 12 second post.
Yeah. And, mm-Hmm.
Um, what I'm trying to figure out if it's even possible, or,
or how, how do you, how do you scale?
That is my, is my question. Right? Good.
Good question. High. Yeah.
If it's high production, if you got an hour
and a half, like that's, like,
that's a whole day for someone.
If we sell a package that's 3, 3, 3
high production posts a day.
Yeah. Like, you know,
like you only can really have one full-time
person for each account.
Now, how do you charge for that full-time person, right.
If they're, they're skilled and, you know,
and they're, they're expensive.
Like in the, the, your, your ad that caught my eye
that I clicked through, you know,
they're either the good people are either
expensive or they're already hired.
Right. So how do you, how do you, how do you scale that?
Right. I think I,
I think I know the answer to your question.
Um, because I, you know, I've, I've, I've been
through that process.
I've had 50 employees.
I had, you know, US employees,
and then I had offshore team as well.
So it's very expensive to be in a very,
like a service industry,
or at least like, you know, to run that type of business.
Mm-Hmm. So, what I've learned in the last, you know,
by downsizing my company,
by restructuring just the organization, um, I was able
to save on a lot of money.
Um, but your editing team
should most likely be outsourced.
All right. And that's 'cause
because the labor cost of working in the Philippines,
or Asia or Europe
or somebody else somewhere else is much like,
it's the same amount of time.
Right. But you're gonna be paying a fraction of
what you would normally pay for a US employee.
'cause us employee, the living standards here are insane.
Right. Especially in ssf.
Like, you gotta be making a certain minimum. Yeah.
It's insane. Like, livable wages is,
is is wild here in California.
Um, Mm-Hmm. So when you hire talent
or like bring someone on your team,
it's like you want one person, like you wanna hire as slow
as possible, in my opinion.
Like whoever that, that that creative person is,
will be responsible for shooting and creative direction.
Um, and then handing that over to editors, one editor,
or many editors, because you can get 10 editors
for the price of one ear.
You know what I mean? Mm-Hmm mm-Hmm.
And that's how you scale it,
because, uh, when you shoot content, it's a lot faster
to shoot content than it is to edit.
Mm-Hmm. So you can batch shoot, which, which,
which is what we do.
So if I was gonna go into a restaurant
and be like, okay, we need,
we need seven pieces of content this week.
Right. I would already have
that listed out in shots, in scripts.
It's like, okay, we're gonna do pouring shots.
We're gonna do, you know, flipping a bottle.
We're gonna get people, uh, cheering.
We're gonna get, you know, walking through the restaurant.
We're gonna get all this stuff in like a five
to six hour window Mm-Hmm.
And I'm gonna get all that raw footage,
and then I'm gonna be like, all right, editors,
here's the game plan.
Here's what we shot, here's the scripts.
Now go edit it in this style.
And now I can go chill out,
or I can go to the next restaurant and the next client,
and I'm gonna do the exact same thing.
And now I've built up a queue of edits for my team to edit.
Meanwhile, I'm able to still produce the content, um,
without getting bogged down with the editing.
Does that make sense? Mm-Hmm.
Oh, yeah. I, I, I follow. Yeah.
Um, that, that would be freaking awesome.
How, how did you vet out overseas editors?
Like, how did you really identify if they had the skill to,
to, or, or I should say, I mean, it's part skill,
part art, right?
And it's how, how, how are you able to convey the,
the just the feel of your experience as a customer
to someone that's, you know, someone that's overseas,
you know, how or, or what were some of the growing pains
that you experienced to, to figure that part of it out?
Well, I will, you know, I've, I've, I've met up
with my overseas team.
I've worked with so many overseas editors.
Um, CH Chan in, in, in the call right now.
He's in, um, I wanna say in Cambodia.
I think he's in Cambodia right now. You remember? Yes.
Um, mm-Hmm. So he is technically overseas editor.
He's extremely talented, you know what I mean?
And, um, and it's like,
there's amazing talented people all over the world, man,
all over the world who are hungry, who are starving,
who are looking for work.
Um, and it really comes down to like, um,
setting very clear expectations in my opinion.
Um, Mm-Hmm. You're gonna get a lot of, like, for example,
running ads, orx, um, ads and, and organic content.
I get a ton of editors who are just reaching out to me like,
Hey, I wanna join your team and stuff.
And I'm looking at their portfolios and I'm like, Hmm.
Like, this isn't someone I'd want
to bring onto the team, or whatever.
So what you want to do is you, you wanna set a bar of
standard of like, okay, here's some
of our best quality videos that have done well for us.
Um, this is the style that we're looking for in an editor,
because like, one editor is not created equal.
Um, Mm-Hmm. For example, Chan like, he's an,
he's AUGC editor
and AVSL editor, um, I'm sure your, your other editors do.
Uh, but from what I've seen, he's really good at cutting,
uh, user generated content.
And he's good at storytelling.
Meanwhile, there's other editors
who are gonna be really amazing or really bad at that,
but really amazing at this more cinematic stuff.
You know, music videos and stuff like that.
Or, um, lifestyle type videos. Mm-Hmm mm-Hmm.
Um, and when you, it's like you can attract those types
of editors and delegate certain jobs to them where
their strengths lie.
'cause what I've learned is not
all editors are created equal.
So when I'm sending a project out, I wanna make sure
that the editor that I'm working with is equipped
with the experience and the skillset
and the enthusiasm to get this, this piece of work done.
Um, I'm not gonna assign the same edit to another one
because I know this guy's gonna take twice as long
and it's gonna come out messed up.
So, yeah.
When you, you know what I mean, it, it, it's just a,
it's just a, a people resources skill, talent type of thing.
So when looking for editors, number one, Upwork, tons
of opportunities there.
Hey, I'm looking for editors who sp who can create this type
of content, X, Y, Z.
Right? You're gonna get a ton of applications. Okay.
You're gonna, you're gonna look at their profiles.
Um, you're gonna see if any of those match any
of the existing content that you have.
Oh, that one looks pretty good. That you have to, you have
to watch their footage as if you're a,
you're, it's your first time too.
You know, you're, you're an
audience member to their content.
So if they're engaging you, it's probably a good sign.
If they're not, it's probably a bad sign.
It's probably sign. Okay.
It's not, this is not the type of person I wanna work
with. Um,
Yeah. I follow,
um, in, in regards to that,
that helps me out a lot.
Thank you for that. In, in regards to the actual, like,
videographer Mm-Hmm.
Are, are you, is that a a, a gig type work position?
Did you bring someone on full-time, part-time W two?
Like, how, how did you scale that aspect of it?
The actual camera person?
So when I did have a really big team, they were full-time,
uh, w two employees, uh,
because we were pumping out
so much content we were shooting every single day.
Um, which is kind of crazy.
Um, and so yeah, we're paying them full-time now,
depending on your situation, like, you may not be, you know,
they may not be working full-time, so it's like,
it doesn't make sense to pay them full-time wages, right?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Exactly.
Yes. So in that case, you know, um,
10 99 definitely works well.
I think it's just really important that you establish
a good working relationship with videographers and creatives
because, you know, they, you know, they're,
they're a rare breed too,
and you don't wanna, like, you don't wanna undercut them
and you don't want to like, overwork them at the same time.
'cause Mm-Hmm. Um, it's like if you can work out a deal,
it's like, Hey, if I, if I had to shoot with you,
it's a six hour shoot, um, you know, I'd be happy.
This is like my rate that I'm willing to pay for this.
Um, would you be okay with that?
Like, you, you have to obviously know how much
you are willing to, to pay.
Like, what's your ceiling? And then mm-Hmm.
If they're cool with that, then all right, great.
If this works, well, then I'm happy to like,
maybe make this more consistent for you.
Um, and then maybe even, uh, turn this into something else.
Like as we get busier as a company. Um, so a follow. Yeah.
You don't wanna like, oh, like each, you can't,
if you can't commit to them
full-time, they can't commit to you.
The, the amount of work needs to be there, right? Mm-Hmm.
So in the beginning, it all has to kind of be contract,
in my opinion, until you have,
let's say you land three clients that are on a three
to six month contract,
and now you have a,
a solid retainer cashflow coming in Mm-Hmm.
That is gonna support their salaries
or their, their contract fees.
Um, and now you have predictable cashflow from that
because if it's gig to gig
and you're paying someone full time, then that's
where it can get really hairy.
Well, I, I gotcha.
Well, once you were able to produce the,
the short form content
or the, the end, the end product for your client who,
who was in charge of actually posting
that or the caption of that?
Like how did you, how did you work through that component
with your, with your clients at that time?
What's up spars? Um, so we,
we have a kind of a different business model.
We don't do like organic content per se.
Um, 'cause we run the ads or like we create the video ads.
But I mean, at the end of the day, content is content.
Um, in other companies that I've worked with
who do like social posting
and things like that, they have
what are called vass virtual assistants, you know,
typically from the Philippines, um, who are mm-Hmm.
Writing, you know, captions, getting the tags,
doing the research, doing the scheduling, uh,
once the content is is ready.
So I gotcha. There's a lot of apps out there
that you can schedule content, uh,
for your accounts, like ahead of time.
Mm-Hmm. Um, make it very simple, very easy.
That way it's not you
or like someone last minute, like, oh crap,
it's like six o'clock.
And I have to, you know, 'cause I've done that before too.
That's not, that's not fun. Right,
Right. Right. Yep.
Um,
So obviously in the beginning
you're always doing everything yourself.
Um, but yeah, like I said, um, affordable labor, um, in,
in other countries is going to give you
so much more leverage, um, versus like, hiring in-house, uh,
US and, um, okay.
Yeah. And, and you know, for example, me, like some of the,
some of my VAs, I don't like to call 'em VAs
'cause they're human beings at the end of the day. Yeah,
Yeah, Yeah. Right.
Um, I've, I've worked with them for, for years, like,
for like seven plus years.
Um, because like, especially the Filipinos, I'm Filipino,
so I'm, I'm kind of biased,
but I, like Filipinos are hardworking, you know, and,
and we're, we're pretty, pretty loyal to at least, um,
the ones that I've hired are very pretty loyal to us.
Mm-Hmm. As employers.
And, um, and they're versatile, you know, and,
and we're smart and we're creative,
and we, we'll get it done.
We'll figure out a way to get it done.
So, um, similar to that process of hiring video editors,
I would do the exact same thing, um,
with virtual assistants.
I, I need a social media manager, a
or a poster copywriter to do x, y,
and Z tasks every single week.
Right? Mm-Hmm. Just get specific with the roles
and the responsibilities and expectations
and guarantee you'll find some people
who, uh, who fit the job.
Nice, man. Cool. Cool.
We, we, we actually, we already have a bid out right now
with, uh, a hotel in downtown San Francisco.
Sweet. Um, to, to, you know, the whole A to Z run their ads,
run their socials, create their content, edit,
community building, all that stuff.
Um, they're, uh, they're kind
of putting their budget together for 2024.
Um, so we're just waiting to hear back from them if they,
uh, agree to our price
or if they wanna negotiate and whatnot.
We actually proposed, um, pricing at a one year contract,
pricing at a two year contract
and pricing at a three year contract.
So, uh, once we, you know, once we can get some traction on
that, that'll definitely, uh,
give us some budget to work with.
Yeah. Um, I guess my, my wife
and her family just got home, so I, I might have
to hop off here pretty soon, but, um, no worries.
I guess one last question here is, uh, in regards
to your structuring on the retainer, like we had asked
for a, a 25% deposit in the beginning Yeah.
To kind of get through the first quarter Mm-Hmm.
Um, and then after the first quarter, then it would be, um,
just a, a monthly fee that we would charge plus a,
a a a commission on what we're able to sell.
Um, but, uh, how, how, how did you structure that part
with the retainer aspect when
you would work with a, a client?
Yeah, it's a little tricky.
Um, especially in the beginning.
Like, I don't know, depending on the size of the company,
from what I've experienced, like, everybody wants
to like measure quality first before committing, um, mm-Hmm.
And, you know, if you throw, at least from my experience,
I can't speak on behalf of everybody,
but, um, like, okay, I want you
to be on a six month contract with me
before we even produce anything.
And they're like, go f**k yourself. Um, um, so,
Oh, man. Uh,
but like I've learned it's really about trust
in this, in this space.
Mm-Hmm. Um, especially like, you know, in content,
it's like people get burned all the time.
They're, they spend a ton of money, doesn't get any results.
Um, yeah. So when I, when I introduce a retainer model,
it's usually after I've produced some
sort of result for them.
Um, and they're happy with, with the quality, because
I gotcha. It, it can burn,
it can burn bridges on both ends with,
like, for example, I was charging one client, um,
pretty, pretty substantial amount for,
for producing some, uh, content.
And I had to pause it
because it wasn't getting the results that I had wanted.
And, and same for him.
So I was like, okay, how do we re-strategize this
and make this actually work?
So it's a win-win.
So I'm always thinking of win-win in that case. Um, mm-Hmm.
And then for them it should be a no-brainer.
Hey, we love this, this is great. This is working. Yeah.
Let's sign on six months. Let's do a year.
Let's get performance deals in, in, in place.
'cause we trust that you,
we trust that you know what you're doing.
Gotcha. Um, but in terms of like upfront, like,
I always accept like a hundred percent payment upfront
because it's like, it's like, I hate doing split payment,
uh, because it basically means one for you,
cashflow is not there. And then, uh,
Yeah. And, and, and the
upfront costs on our tools
and our equipment and the gig work and all that
Stuff. Labor. Yeah.
It, it, mm-Hmm.
It's essential for a service type of business like this to,
to capture cash upfront.
Mm-Hmm. Because down the road 50, that getting
that additional 75 or 50% is a f*****g pain in the ass.
If, you know, you can't reach out, they don't, you know,
they don't respond like it's happening right now. Yeah.
You gotta chase it. Yeah. It, it's happening right now.
It's like the last 50 50 deal
that we've ever done that we're ever gonna do.
And I, I did it even though my wife who's
ACFO, she's like, don't do it.
I have a bad feeling about it. And it turned out to be true.
Mm-Hmm. Um, and like, we've done the work
and now it's like, we are not gonna deliver the rest
of the videos because we're gonna wait for her payment.
And it's just like, it's
just annoying. You know what I mean?
Uh, yeah, I know what you mean.
It always makes it, it makes the opportunity
for it to get uncomfortable.
Exactly. And yeah, just ask for upfront payment.
All right. We'll deliver in x amount of days.
Like, just be clear with the deliverables. Um, Mm-Hmm.
And that's how we work. And then people always ask, well,
it's our first time, da, da, da.
It's like, well, that's how we work,
and there's no questions asked
because we've had bad experiences,
and we want this to be, you know, if you trust us, we,
it's, it's a trust thing.
And if like, if they're apprehensive about investing in you,
then it may not be the best client to work with.
You know what I mean? Um, yeah. Yeah.
I gotcha. I gotcha. Um, well, cool, man.
Thank you so much. I'm glad I, I hopped on,
I had a few free minutes.
My, uh, my wife
and her family actually just flew in from Korea
late last night, so Oh,
Nice. They're,
they're just, uh,
starting with their day here now.
Um, but, uh, yeah, I guess,
is it cool if I just shoot you a DMM in the Slack channel
here and there if I have any questions, or Of course.
Is it you, how often do you do these, uh, zooms
Once a week. Kind
Of like once a Week live calls. Yeah.
Perfect. I'll, uh,
I'll make sure I have the notifications on.
If I get caught up on something I can, I can hop on.
Absolutely. Nick, man, it was, uh, it was good catching up
with you and helping you out.
I hope, I hope it was valuable.
I hope you got something outta it. Oh, yeah,
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Um, appreciate it, John.
Thank you so much for your time.
And, um, yeah, man, we'll, we'll, we'll be in touch.
All right. Take care, Nick. All right. Cheers.
Awesome. Chan, sparse. What's up guys?
How we doing?
How, how are you Doing? Good, man. Are you tired?
I'm I up pretty late today.
Yeah. You woke up pretty late.
Yeah. So that means you're energized,
that means you have energy.
Oh yeah. Okay, cool. Cool man. Um, Chan, how you doing, bro?
I'm, I'm doing good. I'm doing good.
Doing good. Were you able to make any, uh,
affiliate sales on, on vsl.ai?
Oh, no. It was just, uh, I only got leads,
but no conversions.
Um, yeah, I think there's, there's a big opportunity there
to, if you wanted to pursue affiliate stuff,
because it's so, like, it's so easy, you know, it's so easy
to demonstrate the value, you know what I mean?
Um, for others. So, yeah.
But I'm pretty stoked.
Uh, we've got a couple,
we've got some fun things going on for the community.
Sparse is actually, we just brought 'em onto the team
and basically every day we're gonna have something
different, uh, in terms of engagement, um, tutorials,
training, inspiration,
and, uh, sparse is helping out with that.
So I'm really excited about it.
Um, yeah, we've got, we've got an app
that we're building out to help basically
with installation and updates.
So I'm excited about that.
Um, and more trainings coming along the way.
But, um, we'd love to hear Chan about the performance
of, of the VSLs.
Were you able to launch any of 'em?
Um, well, the business owner didn't,
uh, get back to me yet.
Uh, he said it was been busy,
but I am assuming he sent this to his team already,
so I might hear back from him, uh, by the end of the week.
Okay, nice. Yeah, that's awesome.
Um, I, I spoke with, uh,
did you guys ever listen to the five light bulbs training?
Um,
Oh yeah. Yeah. I did
A little bit of that on video tower, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was on Ow.
Um, so I spoke with the,
the creator of that concept.
Um, his name is, uh, Billy Broz.
So I jumped on a call with him, actually, uh, last week.
And I want to get him onto, onto a call
for the community so that he can drop some,
like his own stuff.
He, it's really sick what he, what he's put together.
I'm actually gonna share something right now
that I think is gonna be super
valuable, um, for others as well.
But it's, um, I think it,
it applies directly to video ads.
Lemme just find the screenshot right now
and walk, walk us through it.
'cause I think looking at videos this way
allows us editors to, okay, here it is.
Perfect. I'm gonna share my screen.
All right. So
number one, the first thing, um,
that he talked about is,
let's see,
okay, it looks something like this.
So his whole concept,
his whole concept is, you know, you have light bulb one,
which is customer status quo.
You have, lemme see if I can annotate, can I annotate here?
Okay, yeah. You have light bulb one,
which is customer status quo.
You have light bulb two, which is,
uh, things that they've tried.
And then you have light bulb three, which is your, um,
like your offer or like your unique selling proposition.
Number four is your, your offer.
And then number five is customer's new life.
So basically, like what he was explaining
was from an ad perspective, let's say you're focusing on
light bulb number three, which is in this case,
um, your offer.
So like he was saying, you're gonna make a claim
of some sort, and you need to substantiate that claim.
And the more that you can substantiate a claim,
the more persuasive it's going to be.
Is that making sense? So let's say for example,
in his example, it was, um,
now I don't like this annotation s**t.
Um, he said
like, note taking is important.
Oh, notes are important. Okay?
So like, if you're selling, if you're selling a, a notebook
or like a journal of some sort, right?
Uh, and you wanna make the claim
that taking notes is very important, here's why.
Right? Like if you had the hook of like, um,
why I started taking better notes, right?
Now, you're making a claim.
And now in order for someone to like actually buy,
you have to support that claim.
So he break breaks it down by, okay, there, there are seven,
seven forms of proof, which is,
number one, share a story.
Number two, demonstrate it.
Number three, adding social proof.
Number four, having authority.
Number five, having data around it.
Number six, third party endorsement. Seven.
And, uh, seven is a reason why.
So very similar to kind of like how I've,
I've presented the, like
what we call like a viral video, right?
You have social proof, authority,
like all these persuasive elements.
But what really made it click for me was realizing,
oh, this is how we, we turn
one claim and make it like an ultra
freaking persuasive video.
So let's say, for example, so I think the more,
the more cases that you have,
or I'm sorry, the more, uh, forms of proof
that you have in the video, the stronger it's gonna be.
But he says like, you can just focus on one,
but I'm like, let's throw 'em all in there, right?
So notes are important.
Let's say we're just, we're selling this, uh,
let's say we're selling this journal right here.
Um, and I make the claim why I started taking notes, uh,
why I started taking better notes,
or here's why I believe notes are the most important
thing to your productivity.
Boom, I just made a claim.
Now, if I'm gonna go through this as seven forms of proof,
um, I'm gonna start, let's start with the story, right?
So maybe I'll say, um,
there's a time in college when I never took notes
and I would write them down,
or I would take really bad notes
and I would put 'em on a piece of paper,
and then I would lose them and I wouldn't remember them,
and it was just a pain in the ass.
Um, and so I knew, now I knew at
that time like I was doing something wrong.
So that, that's a story, right?
And it's like, oh, someone could relate to
that in some way, shape, or form.
So that sh and so you can then show the solution.
And then I found this note taking device,
which has helped me improve my retention,
has helped me take better notes, stay organized,
and it's a game changer.
That alone could be an ad, right?
I just made one claim
and I made, I backed it up with one form of proof.
Now, if I were to take it to the next level,
I could demonstrate it and tell that story.
So it's like, all right, notes are important,
and I'm gonna show you exactly why
or how this notebook will change your life
and how you take better notes, right?
And then you can demonstrate the product,
which is pretty self-explanatory.
I think this one is, um, pretty,
pretty common to understand, right?
But now you can combine the story
and the demonstration into one third is social proof.
I think we all know this one.
It's taking somebody else's opinion, throwing it in there.
This is the best, you know, thing for me as a student
or as a mom, or as somebody else.
Number four is authority, which is super important.
So like, who's like the best in the space?
I think in, in his example, he, he applied, um, uh,
Leonardo da Vinci as, uh, as the authority.
So he, he said that he would go to, uh, chat GPT,
and then type in who are some people
who took copious notes in history, right?
And then it would be like, oh,
this person, this person, that person.
And then, okay, tell me more about that.
So now you've actually positioned it as an authority, uh,
of someone who values taking notes.
And now somebody who's now a little bit like on the fence
about it, oh, Leonardo da Vinci, like endorses note taking,
let's go right now.
We've checked off that box.
And, and so yeah, now that's like four pillars
of persuasion that is going
to convince the person at this point,
like, you would be solid.
I think that's a still a really strong ad.
Like for example, in a, in a short form 32nd video,
you may not go through all of this,
but in a vsl,
let's go right now we're showing off all those components,
and we're not just talking about one claim,
we're talking about many claims, I'm sure.
So moving on, like having data around it, did you know that,
um, taking better notes has resulted in 95% more
effectiveness in your ability to think critically,
Harvard, blah, blah, blah.
It's like, oh, s**t, I didn't know
that I need to take better notes.
Right? And just like, just saying this out loud, you're,
you're probably getting more convinced that you need
to take better notes because our,
our brains are wired in this way to like kind
of be skeptics, right?
So if we present this, the information in this format,
then there's no objections that could be made.
There's, there's, it, it closes the gap, the loop
of potential objections and third party endorsement.
You know, um, we could mention, oh, people, um,
from this community recommend, um, our, our, our notebooks
or, uh, this company hires, you know, has used all
of our notebooks in, in their offices, right?
Or like Dell, you know, people
who work at Dell are using this notebook,
and it's, it's been changing the employee's lives.
Um, reason why.
So the number one reason why you need to be, you know,
taking better notes is to improve yourself, period.
Like, if you wanna improve yourself,
this is the reason why you should take better notes.
So I think number seven is still a little bit fuzzy,
but I, from what I took from this, I'm like, this is,
this is game changing when you really break it down,
because you've got
many opportunities to scale a message, right?
So his whole theory is, depending on the light bulb
that you're on, you make that claim.
Um, you can do this for any potential
part of where the customer is at in their journey.
So, you know, if we're starting
with the customer status quo, which is somebody
who is experiencing, you know, a pain of suffering
of some sort, if they're tired of taking notes, uh,
a really ineffective way, then the claim
that you're gonna make is very different.
Instead of saying notes are important,
you're gonna say like, um, you know, the old way of
of taking notes is, is wrong,
or like, it's ineffective to take handwritten notes
or, you know what I mean?
You're, you're meeting the customer where they're at, um,
and then you're creating the proof around it.
So that to me makes sense.
Yeah, take it makes perfect sense.
And it's like, I think this is one of the best ways
of looking at video ads in general, is
that it is an argument, right?
I didn't, I wasn't speech and debate,
but I didn't do debate.
I did speech, which is more of like performance
and acting and stuff like that.
But when you, when you can back up your,
your claims when you're speaking about something,
we were trying to convince somebody of something,
it's the same thing in a video ad, right?
And, and our ability as editors is to make it a story
that makes it like engaging to watch.
Because if someone's just like saying it out loud, you know,
it doesn't make it as enjoyable to watch.
But as editors, that's when we add the bells
and whistles to make it look cool.
But ultimately, I believe if you're making a strong argument
in your video, then your chances of of, I mean,
your conversion rate's gonna gonna boost for sure.
Like, retention's gonna boost.
And I think for short form content,
if say you're not doing a 20 minute VSL
or whatnot, then you just focus on one of these elements
of proof or two at a time in a 32nd, one minute video.
Um, and then you create 10 videos of those
that all independently have, like their own,
it's the same claim, but like a different way of proving it.
And then that's how you can split test the message
to see which one resonates the most.
Yeah, exactly what I was going to say on short form,
taking just one proof of, uh, I'm sorry,
what were they called again?
Okay, yeah, let me pull 'em up. Um, the
Seven Yeah. Form of proof.
Yeah. Yeah. Seven forms
Of proof. Yeah. Just taking one
a, like having a big asset
and just split testing each form, like making one claim
and testing it with one form of proof.
And if you, if you're doing short form, right,
and then having the most,
and then you see what kinda resonates most with the buyer
that you are targeting as well.
Yeah, absolutely.
I think this is like, what I love about this concept is
that you're breaking down the, the principles.
I think this is, I mean,
what people would call first principles thinking,
but you're breaking it down to the, the,
the core concepts of marketing.
And I think that's ultimately like where people become
confused about editing or copywriting
or videography or any type of marketing messaging
or social media is
because they're lacking the understanding of the claims
that they're making, or like the video content
that they're producing because they're, they're missing.
It's a big knowledge gap of, um, you know,
'cause ultimately what he wants is
you gotta take a person from here who,
who doesn't believe in you,
to over here, who believes in you.
So it's, it's a matter of beliefs, changing their beliefs
around your product or service and, um, getting them to buy.
So this is why, I mean, it's,
I don't know if anybody has done sales before,
but it's kind of like that as well.
I mean, it's the same thing, like person to person sales.
Has anybody done that? Like,
Does as freelancers, you go this all the time.
Yeah, freelancer, I mean, as a freelancer,
I feel like this is all the stuff that you need
to actually get clients as well, right?
Right. Um, because at the end of the day, you're trying
to win a sale, right?
I can demonstrate to you that I have the skills,
here's my story, you know, I came from nothing
and now I am pursuing my passion.
I have a lot of clients under my belt.
Here's what they said about me.
Um, here's John from econ vids, he has a testimonial.
Um, right. Here's the data.
Like here's some of the ads that have performed super well
for my clients, and this is like the click-through rates
and the conversion rates, right?
So the more that you can add, I know for me if, um,
it's say I'm hiring somebody, I'd be like, oh,
I'd love, oh, that's awesome.
Oh man, you did all that. Because like most of the time
when freelancers come to me, they're just being like, Hey,
here's my portfolio.
And I'm like, okay, great. Right? But what else?
And, and sparse. I think the thing that stood out
for me when you reached out, um, when I did
that job posting was, your message
to me was like on point.
It like, it like struck me
and versus everybody else who didn't really understand
what I was looking for, I was like,
I would need a direct response editor.
I'm looking for someone who really likes direct response
and marketing and ads.
And when you sent your reply, it was like,
it was all the proof I needed to make the decision.
So, um, I hope that's okay. What
Was the pitch?
What was It? What did he, what is
It? Oh, I said, uh, what,
what, what was, uh, what did he pitch?
Oh, yeah, I, I wanted to break it down for you as well.
Actually, let me pull it up as well.
I kind of remember a little bit, but
It's funny. Yeah.
I think sometimes, yeah,
But this is one, Go ahead.
Yeah, continue. Yeah,
but I was, I was saying that this is one thing that
once I started structuring my proposals
or cover letters on Upwork like this, my response rate, just
like when you start to think of, okay,
what is this guy looking for?
And instead of just being like, oh, hello, it's me.
My name is first, I do this more than, okay,
I understand what your problem is.
This is something that I've done.
And okay, if you don't believe me, this is like,
check it, check out this thing.
And giving them a direct linking instead of a big portfolio
that, okay, this is something
that directly relates with you mm-Hmm.
And then just having a call to action that I think I said
to you that, okay, click this link, book a call with me.
Let's jump on a call. Mm-Hmm.
Something like this, but I, and pull it up here for chat.
I'll add one thing to that. And I think it's so important
as freelancers to have some sort
of call booking opportunity.
Um, especially because most of the time you're working
with like, you know, business people
who are looking to hire.
So it's like we have limited time
and it's like the quicker
that we can get on a conversation quicker than we can decide
if this is a good fit or not.
Um, but I do agree with you only sending
relevant information over to the prospect
that is relatable to the job at hand, right?
So when I have clients coming in, they're like, Hey,
I'm looking for of this product, you know,
and my, I'm not gonna show them my whole portfolio
of 7,000 videos.
I'm just gonna show them like two. Yeah.
This is what's similar to you. Um, yeah.
But do you have it? Do you wanna share it?
Yeah, I have it here. Yeah.
So I just had a hook that I love what you're doing at,
I understand what you're doing.
It's a great thing for video editors
and I had a compliment for you as well
that even I might take a few templates.
It's really cool. And moving on, I have a quick intro
that I'm a video editor, uh, direct response is
what I'm focusing on.
And then immediately I was like, okay, one
of my recent wins was with Mindvalley's Trailer.
It turned out to be the top performing, uh,
creative in the lineup.
Uh, it got the green, my value green light,
so you can check it out here.
That's one video that I gave you.
And also I crafted this other direct response video.
Check it out here. Hmm. That's it.
Uh, and after I was like, oh,
your job listing got me super stoked.
Yeah. It's another kind of compliment
and team, let's team up.
If you want to team up, count me in
and if you want to talk more, let's, uh, book a call.
Here's a direct link you can see when I'm available.
Like, we don't have to go back
and forth that, oh, are you available at this time?
Yeah. You don't even have to message me to book a call.
So it's really easy for you to do it as well.
And then you have all the information in
a short message for you.
I love that. That dude sparse.
Let's, let's put together like an SOP for some
of the freelancers here because dude, I think
that's super valuable.
And from, from the employer side, the thing
that I was looking for is, Hey,
you looked into me like you did additional research,
then just click, I'm interested in this job.
You know, like you showed intention of, hey,
like this is really cool,
or I can see how you're adding value,
or, you know what I mean?
That tells me that this person is genuinely
interested in the position.
Um, and so Chan,
I think I wanna go circle back to really quick.
Like I know you are working with certain people
who maybe you're not aligned with, like
what they're saying and stuff.
Um, I think it, that's an opportunity to
f*****g put your foot down about like who you are
as a creative and like what you stand for
and what you want to be working with
and who you want to be working with, right?
This is so important as a creative to identify
this is like, these are my values
and this is what I believe in,
and I'm not going to like, settle for anything less.
And this is what I've had to learn
as an agency owner is like saying no to cl a lot of clients
that I don't think are a good fit for me and my team,
because those are the people who drain your energy
and who pay the least amount of money.
So you wanna be working with people
who are gonna be exciting to work with, who
inside the edit you're like, this is stoked.
I'm stoked about this. I'm stoked what they're saying,
you know this, I'm totally aligned with what they're saying.
This is amazing. Um, versus the opposite
because when you do the opposite,
you're basically not creating boundaries.
And I've had to learn this myself.
You're not creating boundaries for yourself
and then you're allowing other people
to cross that boundary.
Um, and what that's gonna do is just going to eat
and suck up your energy.
And that precious creative energy is what you are valued
for or not what you're valued.
That, like, that is your value.
That is your core gift, you know,
and you want to protect that as much as you can.
Thank you so much for the course.
I recently learned this community that you're building this
lesson is very valuable, this lesson
because I offered like for, I'm gonna do some free stuff
for things like these calls for, for a friend,
but I knew I didn't want to do it.
Why? Because I have so much crap going on already.
And in the back of my mind I was like,
I don't wanna do this, I don't wanna do this, you know,
and he's like, Hey, he's like following up with me.
Like, where's the thing?
You know, he's someone that's doing
what you're doing and doing block.
And eventually I was just like,
dude, I can't do this for you.
I'm sorry. Um, it's really helpful.
I'm gonna have, have to get paid to do this
because I just don't have the time and resources
and I have other people who are paying me
and I gotta put them priority.
And so once I was clear about the boundaries
that I was setting, 'cause I was, I, it's always like a fear
of what they're gonna think of you afterwards,
but in the end you respected me for it.
And he is like, oh, that's cool man. All right, moving on.
And then I'll have to think about it.
I don't have to do it, but if I had still agreed to it,
I would've done it and I would've been drained doing it
and I would've cost myself more time and energy.
Um, and then he wouldn't have known that I was unhappy
with the decision I made.
Does that make sense? So
anyways, I hope that's helpful, Jan.
That's, that's really helpful.
Um, awesome guys, that wraps up today's call.
I hope you guys got some, um, some tips outta that one.
I think spars you
and I will talk, maybe we can put together some sort
of best practices for freelancers.
I think that's so awesome. Um,
and then share a case study
of ourself, you know what I mean?
Um, well good s**t guys.
It's good seeing you and I will talk
to you guys in the, in the community.
Great. Sounds good. All
Awesome.
Have a good night guys. You too. Bye.